2009年春天
在阔别舞台10年之后
50岁的迈克尔·杰克逊精心策划制作了
一场全新的演出
他的观众只是一些技术人员和舞蹈演员
他们见证了迈克尔
为重回舞台设计的演出
这部电影由录像的镜头片段组成
从3月到6月这段排练期间
它是对迈克尔的独家珍藏
也是最初演出的内容
在6月25日
迈克尔和他的团队
离开了8天去伦敦
做最后一次服装彩排
50场演唱会门票空前地销售一空
经过迈克尔·杰克逊遗产负责人的同意
也多亏一些捕获了这精彩画面的相机
成就这部迈克尔献给全世界歌迷和观众们
最热切的礼物
就是这样
2009年4月15日
你从哪儿来
我来自荷兰 到这儿要花大约...10小时
就像穿越了整个世界来这儿试镜
我告诉了家里所有的兄弟
我要在迈克尔前面的舞台上热舞了
我为他而跳舞
我不在乎是否成功 我什么都不在乎
谢谢你 迈克尔 我太兴奋了
你鼓舞了我一生
我的力量...你是我跳舞的原因
记得我还是个孩子的时候
和我妈妈看"颤栗"的MTV
我觉得那是全世界最棒的表演
我睡觉醒来做的第一件事
不是吃饭 而是打开音乐 开始...
开始...跳舞 在大街上跳太空步
我想...我要...
我一定要跟你一起站在舞台上...
实际上 我成功了...太神奇了...
我来自澳大利亚...
在试镜之前...
我还要再等两天
它就是我的目的地
这只是刚刚开始...
我还没站在舞台上呢
我想象不到在伦敦的第一场演出时
后台会发生什么
我想象着未来
我不知道做完这个后还能干什么
因为这是迈克尔
我想要跳舞 你知道我的意思
我的勇气来自...你
你鼓舞了我 也使我鼓舞了别人
生活是艰辛的 我一直在寻找...
寻找能够激励我的事 给我...
一种人生意义...去信仰某些事
就是这样
献给歌迷们...
我们的演出就要开始了
所有灯光全熄灭
我们要以烟火壮观开场
我们想要火花的滋滋声 爆裂声和呼啸声
我们把我们的录像称作 瞬间回忆
太空人从那个门架里出来了
悬浮在舞台之上
听着光彩夺目的景象和录像信息
一点一点 一点一点地...
MJ出现在舞台之上
迈克尔一声令下 我们开始了...
迈克尔·杰克逊: 就是这样
Wanna Be Starting Something
You got to be starting something
I said you wanna be starting something
Starting something
It's too high to get over
You're stuck in the middle
And the pain is thunder
It's too high to get over
Too low to get under
You're stuck in the middle
And the pain is thunder
You love to pretend that you're good
When you're always up to no good
So your tongue became a razor
Someone's always trying to start my baby crying
At this lonely night
You got to be starting something
I said you wanna be starting something
Starting something
It's too high to get over
You're stuck in the middle
And the pain is thunder
It's too high to get over
Too low to get under
You're stuck in the middle
And the pain is thunder
You're a vegetable, you're a vegetable
Still they hate you, you're a vegetable
You're just a buffet, you're a vegetable
They eat off of you, you're a vegetable
He ha.
你不想要那么多 不是吗
要...更有节奏感
我感觉那部分不够
这就像紧跟在谁旁边
- 节奏不对 - 好吧 应该这样
该这样
我知道这都是因为爱
- 会好的 - 我们能行
When love is magical
As how I feel
Without the world knows what worth to explain
To tell you I love you
迈克尔·杰克逊最后的演出就是在这儿
在2006年伦敦的世界音乐大奖典礼上
就是这样 就是这样
我爱你们
我们爱你
我要...我要唱我的歌迷想听的歌
这真的是...最后的谢幕了
好吗
7月份见
Cant feed your baby
Then don't have a baby
Don't think maybe
Can't feed your baby
I'm trying, trying
Baby's slowly dying
You got to be starting something
I said you wanna be starting something
It's too high to get over
Too low to get under
You're stuck in the middle
And the pain is thunder
It's too high to get over
Too low to get under
You're stuck in the middle
Yeah, yeah
Lift your head up and scream out to the world
I know I am someone, let the truth unfurl
No one can hurt you now
Cause you know what's true
I'm believe in me
So you believe in you
Help me sing it
Ama ma se, ma ma sa, ma ma coo sa
Sing it to the world
Sing it alone
Ama ma se, ma ma sa, ma ma coo sa
Help me play it
I said you wanna be starting something
You got to be starting something
Said you wanna be starting something
Starting something
非常...非常高兴见到你们
谢谢你们能来
我们就是要找到全世界最好的舞者
然后把他们聚在一起
在迈克尔·杰克逊演出时的舞蹈演员
是迈克尔·杰克逊的延续
他们是这个男人的延续
在他的世界里...
所有事情都更加夸大 更加强烈
很好 谢谢
下一组 女士们 好极了
就是说非常完美 激情四射 能震撼舞台的舞者
但是如果你没那么好 诠释不出那种感觉
就不能得到那份工作
迈克尔·杰克逊"就是这样"的
正式舞蹈演员是...
天哪 在这儿呢
伙计们 看这儿 得了吧
相信我 亲爱的
今天真够呛 我们要被烤了
它是升降机的速度 也是烤面包机的速度
看到天空预示着开始
保持你们的肩膀平行 保持重心
就像一把枪
占据了一个好位置
你要站出来...
- 你感觉到开始了吗 - 是的 感觉到了
很好 再来一次
Jam
Nation to nation all the world must come together
Face the problems that we see.
Then maybe somehow we can work it out.
I asked my neighbor for a favor.
She said later.
What has come of all the people?
Have we lost love of what it's about?
I have to find my peace cuz no one seems to let me be
False prophets cry of doom. What are the possibilites?
I told my brother there'll be problem,
Times and tears for fears.
But we must live each day like it's the last.
Go with it. Go with it.
Jam, it aing t too much stuff.
It aing t too much
It aing t too much for me to
Jam, it aing t too much stuff.
It aing t Don't you
It aing t too much for me to
Jam. It aing t too much stuff.
It aing t too much
It aing t too much for me to.
Jam. It aing t too much stuff.
It aing t Don't you
It aing t too much for me to
It aing t too much for me to jam
Jam. It aing t too much stuff.
Jam, It aing t, Don't you
Aing t too much for me.
Jam. Jam.
It aing t too much stuff.
Aing t too much for me.
Get on it get on it give it baby
Give it to me
Got to give it you just wanna give it
我们是摄影背景 穿梭在绿光屏之间
我们要从"操练"到"她最后的呼吸"
再到"他们不在乎我们"
这部电影真的很精彩
因为他们把人数翻倍了
也就是说 我们11个人会变成1100个人
这真的太绝了 我们都很兴奋
迈克尔今天要来
- 我的偶像在这儿呢 - 迈克尔在这儿
他在这儿
这样我们造出成千上万的人
迈克尔 首先你喜欢这样吗
- 是的 动作很不错 - 好的
挺好 不过最后太扩散了
那你要停在最大效果上以它作为结束吗
你可以无穷无尽
是啊不过不能超过...
是啊
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
- 是啊也许9个舞蹈演员就够了 - 10个就好
10个 好吧
就是那样
再来一次...6 7 8...
Who's there?
Skin head
Dead head
Everybody gone bad
Situation
Speculation
Everybody allegation
In the suite
On the news
Everybody dog food
Bang bang shock dead
Everybody's gone mad
All I wanna say is that
They don't really care about us
Tell me what has become of my rights
Am I invisible 'cause you ignore me?
Your proclamation promised me free liberty, now.
I'm tired of being the victim of shame
They're throwing me in a class with a bad name
I can't believe this is the land from which I came
Skin head
Dead head
Everybody gone bad
Trepidation
Speculation
Everybody allegation
Beat me
Bash me
You can never trash me
Hit me
Kick me
You can never get me
All I wanna say is that
They don't really care about us
This will go down in history
As the greatest demonstration for freedom
In the history of our mission.
Came the day we read your history
Some things in life they just don't wanna see
But if Martin Luther was living
He wouldn't let this be
All I wanna say is that
They don't really care about us
Give me, on fire.
All I wanna say is that
They don't really care about us
Can't you wrong or right me
All I wanna say is that
They don't really care about us
That's a box of be it
All I wanna say is that
They don't really care about us
继续鼓掌 继续喝彩
渐渐使灯光变暗
多利安·霍利 和声领唱
The city winks a sleepless eye
Hear her voice
调子感觉很好 MJ 感觉很好
Sweet seducing sighs
就停在那儿
Into the night time
Four walls won't hold me tonight
If this town
Is just an apple
Then let me take a bite
If they say why, why,
Tell 'em that it's human nature
Why, why, does he do me that way
If they say
Why, why, tell 'em that it's human nature
Why, why does he do me that way
Reaching out
To touch a stranger
Electric eyes are ev'rywhere
See that girl
She knows I'm watching
She likes the way I stare
If they say
Why, why, tell 'em that it's human nature
Why, why, does he do me that way
If they say
Why, why, tell 'em that it's human nature
Why, why does he do me that way
I like loving this way
Looking out
Across the morning
Where the city's heart begins to beat
See that girl
She knows I'm watching
She likes the way I stare
If they say
Why, why, tell 'em that it's human nature
Why, why, does he do me that way
If they say
Why, why, tell 'em that it's human nature
Why, why does he do me that way
If they say
Why, why, tell 'em that it's human nature
Why, why, does he do me that way
Why, why, why
Why, why does he do me that way
If they say
Why, why, why
Tell them
I like loving this way
Why
Why.
离迈克出现还差几秒钟
镜头转入
然后吉尔达继续唱歌
他来这儿干什么
萨姆 停 这次的不错
我们停吧
很不错
- 好的 布鲁斯... - 什么事 先生
迈克尔的彩排很棒 我们可以做到
- 可以开拍了吗 - 可以
伙计们 我们马上开拍 开始吧
- 转入 - 开始
你想怎么样
要我像他们在电影里一样数到3吗
伙计们 那就是暗号
抱歉 你们是不是还没太搞清楚
不 我们很清楚了
- 都是嘶嘶声 - 但周围都是嘶嘶声
- 都是嘶嘶声 - 好
他在等我的动作 马上
我以为...迈克尔
我告诉他们 你一转向观众就开始
- 你想要... - 我想先转过来 - 好
- 面对观众 没什么的 - 好的
我暗示了之后 我们就开始
问题是你怎么看到镜头
从遮檐到城市的转换
我会凭感觉 我会感觉屏幕的变换
好 现在都是嘶嘶声 嘶嘶声 然后
出现"犯罪高手" 观众们就要疯狂了
摄像机会慢慢越过遮檐
As he came into the window
Was a sound of a crescendo
He came into her apartment
He left the bloodstains on the carpet
She ran underneath the table
He could see she was unable
So she ran into the bedroom
She was struck down
It was her doom
Annie, are you ok
Are you ok
Are you ok, Annie
Annie, are you ok
You ok
Are you ok, Annie
Annie, are you ok
You ok
You ok, Annie
Annie, are you ok
You ok
Are you ok, Annie
Annie, are you ok
Will you tell us that you're ok
And then a sound of a window
That he struck you
A crescendo, Annie
He came into your apartment
He left the bloodstains on the carpet
Then you ran into the bedroom
You were struck down
It was your doom
Annie, are you ok
You ok
Are you ok, Annie
Annie, are you ok
You ok
Are you ok, Annie
Annie, Are you ok
You ok
Are you ok, Annie
You've been hit by
You've been struck by
A smooth criminal
So they came into the outway
It was Sunday
What a black day
Mouth to mouth resuscitation
Heartbeats intimidations
Annie, are you ok
You ok
Are you ok, Annie
Annie, are you ok
You ok
Are you ok, Annie
Annie, are you ok
You ok
Annie, are you ok,
Are you ok, Annie
You ok
Annie, are you ok
Are you okay, Annie
Will you tell us that you're ok
And then a sound of a window
That he struck you
A crescendo, Annie
He came into your apartment
He left the bloodstains on the carpet
Then you ran into the bedroom
You were struck down
It was your doom
Annie, are you ok
You ok
Are you ok, Annie
You've been hit by
You've been struck by
A smooth criminal
Annie, are you ok
Will you tell us that you're ok
And then a sound of a window
That he struck you
A crescendo, Annie
He came into your apartment
He left the bloodstains on the carpet
Then you ran into the bedroom
You were struck down
It was your doom
Annie, are you ok
Will you tell us that you're ok
And then a sound of a window
That he struck you
A crescendo, Annie
He came into your apartment
He left the bloodstains on the carpet
Then you ran into the bedroom
You were struck down
It was your doom Annie
You've been hit by
You've been struck by
A smooth criminal
非常好 非常好
你喜欢这调子?
我作为音乐总监 觉得非常棒
因为我需要歌手们亲自上阵
MJ总是亲自参与所有的一切
他知道自己所有的唱片
所有歌曲的拍子和调子
这里听起来有点怪 拍子要再重点?
好 这调子不太对 所以想象一下那调子
不 不 不 别变信号音
现在还不要变信号音
- 还不变吗 - 不 不 不 就滑过去...
- 我们找到调子了 - 我们找到了 但并不是这样的
明天我们做一下校音
这正是我们需要做的
没找到调子之前 别开始
我知道 所以我们现在才在找调子啊
我们需要你做校音
因为除了你需要听 没人能听得出来
有的人也许不想从这基本的开始
我想要我写这首歌时的调子 听到的调子
还有录音出来的调子
这就是我的全部要求
是的 我们就是要这样的感觉
应该已经离你的要求不远了
你要听起来更高兴
你知道我的意思吧
只有你可以决定 是吧
"听起来更高兴" 真有趣的说法
但是你知道...你明白我的意思 是吧
没错吧
再来一次 从最开始
我们来好好找找调子
不 不 你们得再动情点
- 这里有情感爆发 - 没错
你们没有爆发出来
有一瞬间 应该让感情爆发出来 明白吗
好吧 伙计们 有两个小节是从...
至少一个小节
好的 从刚才那儿再来一次
看看我们能找到什么相似之处
1 2 3 4
Hey, pretty baby with the high heels on!
U give me fever like I'm never ever known!
I feel your fever from miles around.
I'll pick you up in my car we'll paint the twon red.
Just kiss me baby.
And tell me twice that you're the one for me.
The way you make me feel!
You real turn me on!
You knock me off of my feet!
My lonely days are gone!
这地方我会给你手势 我给手势
不能随意来
伙计们 女伴舞得开始跳了
我们配合还不默契 我会给手势的
你们得看着我做这个动作 好吗
I never felt so in love before
Just promise baby u'll love me forever more
I swear I'm keeping you satisfied
'cause u're the one for me
The way you make me feel
You real turn me yours
You knock me off of my feet now
再来一遍
像我们排练的一样
很好 很好
就是这里
你想降八度吗
可以了 不用降 那样太快了
- 好的 我同意 - 好的
- 只是后面... - 别管它了
轻轻推上去就好
MJ 我们装了鼓风机 就在舞台中央
我没听清楚 再说一遍
到时会有风扇 在舞台下面 为你设计的
就在那儿
很好 注意 迈克尔
再说一次 女士们先生们
有请全世界最棒的乐队
杰克逊五兄弟
大家一起鼓掌 来吧
When I had you to myself
I didn't want you around
Out in a crowd
But someone picked you from the bunch
Take a second look
To show you that I love you
Back in your heart
Blind to let you go
Let you go, baby
But now since I've seen you
I want you back
Yes I do now
Ooh ooh baby
I want you back
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Na na na na
I want you back
伙计们 我必须得说
当我试图听耳机时
就像有人把拳头打进我耳朵里
我很难听清
我知道你们的初衷是好的 但实在是...
试试调整一下我的耳机 好吗
带着爱的感觉去试试 L-O-V-E
迈克尔
尽管不那么容易办到
迈克尔 重复一下 我听不到你 先生
你们升高音量时 我很难适应耳机
用你自己亲爱的耳朵试试
对
就像有人把拳头...
打进你耳朵里一样
好吧
我想听耳机但没法听
我正在适应这个情况
好的 迈克尔 在音量或者混音方面
怎么调整耳机才能让你听得清
音量降低点就好
请把音量降低点
还有什么别的吗 迈克尔
想多听到些什么吗
多些声音或者多些...
不用
好的 迈克尔 下首歌结束之后
如果依旧不符合你的要求 请跟我们说
好的
谢谢
你想从哪儿开始继续
- "停下来 你拯救的爱" - "停下来 你拯救的爱"
When we played tag in grade school
You wanted to be It.
But chasing boys was just a fad
You crossed your heart you'd quit.
When we grew up you traded
Your promise for my ring
Now just like back to grade school
You're doing the same old thing!
Stop! The love you save may be your own!
Darling, take it slow
Or some day you'll be all alone.
You'd better stop the love you save may be your own!
Darling, look both ways before you cross me
You're headed for the danger zone.
上帝保佑你们
You and I must make a pact
We must bring salvation back
Where there is love
I'll be there
I'll reach out my hand to you
I have faith in all you do
Just call my name
And I'll be there
I'll be there to comfort you
I'll build my world of dreams around you
I'm so glad I found you yeah
I'll be there with a love so strong
I'll be your strength
You know I'll keep holding on
Baby yet you ever find someone new
I know he better be good to you
'Cause if he doesn't
Then I'll be there
I'll be there
一起唱
I'll be there.
Just call my name
I'll be there
There.
我要说 杰克 杰梅因 马龙
提托 兰迪 我爱你们
约瑟夫和凯瑟琳 上帝保佑你们 我爱你们
请原谅我的嗓子痛 请理解
I will be
There.
- 灭灯 - 请保持后台清洁
把特殊灯光去掉
让侧影进来
我和那些伴舞们 我们和他一起排练
一周两三次
有时候我们练普拉提 抻拉筋骨
还有芭蕾和一些物理疗法
大家都能在一起
我看他们这样做 这是什么
这是俄式跳法吗
这才是俄式跳法
如果巴雷什尼科夫这么跳
你们这么跳 都是一样的
再来一次
是应该上下运动 对吧
我觉得不能随便动 而是手在动
应该更流畅 明白吗
我反正没什么可动的
伴舞们 音乐起
很好伙计们
"我只是不能停止爱你"
朱迪斯
如果迈克尔准备好了请告诉我
谢谢
你会喜欢的 奥特加
- 奥特加... - 开始吧
要的就是这种精神
1 2 3
这里多加点回声
Each time the wind blows
I hear your voice so
I call your name
Whispers at morning
Our love is dawling
Heaven's glad you came
You know how I feel
This thing can't go wrong
I'm so proud to say I love you
Your love's got me high
I long to get by
My life aing t worth living
If I can't be with you
I hear your voice now
You are my choice now
The love you bring
Heaven's in my heart
At your call I hear harps
And angels sing
You know how I feel
This thing can't go wrong
I can't live my life without you
I just can't hold on
I feel we belong
My life aing t worth living
If I can't be with you
I just can't stop loving you
And if I stop
Then tell me just what will I do
I just can't stop loving you
At night when the stars shine
I pray in you I'll find
A love so true
When morning awakes me
Will you come and take me
I'll wait for you
You know how I feel
This thing can't go wrong
I'm so proud to say I love you
I do
This thing can't go wrong
This feeling's so strong
Well, my life aing t worth living
If I can't be with you
I just can't stop loving you, Oh
I just can't stop loving you
And if I stop
Then tell me, just what will I do
I just can't stop loving you
We can change all the world tomorrow
We can sing songs of yesterday
I can say, hey...farewell to sorrow
This is my life and I
Want to see you for always
I just can't stop loving you
No, baby
And if I stop
Then tell me, just what will I do
I just can't stop loving you
Know I do girl!
And if I stop
Then tell me, just what will I do
I just can't stop loving you
And if I stop
Then tell me, just what will I do
Because
I just can't stop
I just can't stop, baby
I just can't stop loving
I just can't stop
I just can't stop, baby
Yeah.
I just can't stop
I just can't stop loving
You
别让我...别让我唱那么大声
我不该唱这么大声...
我只是在热身
现在我是在努力开嗓
为什么要让我唱
我现在不该唱的
不行 不行
- 你最好唱 - 不 不 不
我得开嗓
你没法不唱 MJ
- 不 我不能唱 不该唱 - 好吧
不应该唱
- 你感觉来了 你可以... - 不 不行
你能允许自己不跟着感觉走吗
不行 我不能唱...
你可以唱 但我得保护嗓子
听这个
就是这样
今天几号 现在几点
我们已经快完工了
正在拍电影里的最后一场
"就是这样"影片内容
今天我们要拍摄"战栗"的新片段
3D效果的
看我的3D眼镜酷吗
- 非常酷 - 好的
我觉得戴这个眼镜帅极了
我看起来有这么老吗
大家注意 演员入镜
摄像师 各就各位
请演员准备好
准备录影
开始
这个人应该很快出现在镜头里
- 向上看镜头 - 看镜头
迈克尔 那里会打灯
- 灯还没打过去 - 告诉他
掘墓人 看镜头
对了 继续往前走
继续
对了
镜头推进 演员举起手来
好极了
到镜头前面来
把手举到镜头中心 好的
走出镜头
停 太棒了
谢谢大家
我们把这个称为"僵尸新娘和僵尸新郎"
在"战栗"中 他们会在回廊里举行婚礼
战栗
黑暗降临大地
午夜将近
恶魔爬出洞穴寻找新鲜血液
左邻右舍 不论是谁
家家惊魂
不肯交出灵魂的人
将被困在地狱中
尸体慢慢腐烂
"Thriller"
Its close to midnight and something evils lurking in the dark
Under the moonlight you see a sight that almost stops your heart
You try to scream but terror takes the sound before you make it
You start to freeze as horror looks you right between the eyes,
You're paralyzed
Cause this is thriller, thriller night
And no ones gonna save you from the beast about to strike
You know its thriller, thriller night
Youre fighting for your life inside a killer, thriller tonight
You hear the door slam and realize theres nowhere left to run
You feel the cold hand and wonder if youll ever see the sun
You close your eyes and hope that this is just imagination
But all the while you hear the creature creepin up behind
You're out of time
Cause this is thriller, thriller night
There aint no second chance against the thing with forty eyes
You know its thriller, thriller night
You're fighting for your life inside a killer,thriller
恶魔狂喜地呼号
你是如此美味 如此乖巧
步伐坚定 激起反抗
如雕塑般钉在原地
想要逃跑 想要尖叫
但你再也看不到太阳了
一旦你发现秘密
他们会用冰冷的手结束你的性命
That it's a thriller, thriller night
Cause I can thrill you more than any ghost would dare to try
Girl, this is thriller, thriller night
So let me hold you tight and share a killer, diller, chiller,
要确保有人在那里
给迈克尔打闪光灯 其他都做得非常好
能再来几次吗 10次怎么样
- 当然 - 很合理
之后是烟火场景
我们会演示一些烟火组合
一起来摇滚吧
今天我们会检查水晶吊灯
还有演出所用的设备
让杂技演员和舞蹈演员排练一下
我们要调整角度 反复看效果
制作道具责任重大 也很有趣
因为我们要制作演身上的装饰
和迈克尔合作25年来 我们第一次制作这样的东西
我们在"贝利·珍"的服装上采用闪光材料
切割打磨好好的石头 反光效果很强
需要戴上太阳镜避免刺眼
我们用于演出的物品是独创的
专门为迈克尔量身打造的
我们和荷兰的科学家研究
和加州的部门商量用施华洛世奇水晶
我们尽力做到最好 因为这是迈克尔的演出
- 今晚这个没问题吗 - 是的
不按照顺序排练 我想让迈克尔
决定什么时候启用升降台
在"避开"开始的时候
- 要配上音乐吗 - 可以
我们能试一下吗
- 可以 听你的 - 好的
- 以防万一 谢谢你 迈克尔 - 不客气
这是MJ 勇敢的先生
- 我相信你 - 谢谢
只是为了保证安全 谢谢
你以前用过这个
MJ 这只是一般高度 还可以升得更高
这是低空高度
为什么告诉我这个 你知道
看到了吧 什么意思
就是为了取笑我
你知道我想升得更高
愿上帝保佑你 肯尼
大家好
好的
- 这位置能看到歌迷吗 - 是的
迈克尔 请等等
谢谢
- 这很好 - 是吗 稳当吗
是的
好极了
这真是有纪念意义 迈克尔重回升降台
- 我们爱你 迈克尔 - 我也爱你们
"Just Beat It"
They told him don't you ever come around here
Don't wanna see your face, you better disappear
The fire's in their eyes and their words are really clear
So beat it, just beat it
You better run, you better do what you can
Don't wanna see no blood, don't be a macho man
You wanna be tough, better do what you can
So beat it, but you wanna be bad
Just beat it, beat it, beat it, beat it
No one wants to be defeated
Showing how funky and strong is your fight
It doesn't matter who's wrong or right
Just beat it, beat it
Beat it, beat it
Beat it, beat it, beat it, beat it
Beat it
No one wants to be defeated
Showing how funky and strong is your fight
It doesn't matter who's wrong or right
Just beat it, beat it, beat it, beat it
No one wants to be defeated
Showing how funky and strong is your fight
It doesn't matter who's wrong or right
Beat it, beat it, beat it, beat it
No one wants to be defeated
Showing how funky and strong is your fight
It doesn't matter who's wrong or who's right
Just beat it, beat it, beat it, beat it
No one wants to be defeated
Showing how funky and strong is your fight
It doesn't matter who's wrong or right
Just beat it, beat it
No one wants to be defeated
Showing how funky and strong is your fight
It doesn't matter who's wrong or who's right
Just beat it, beat it
No one wants to be defeated
Showing how funky and strong is your fight
It doesn't matter who's wrong or right
我们要这样做
在做那个撩拨的动作之前
我拉下夹克 边演边唱"避开"
感觉像被火烧一样
- 我想知道最后一段是什么 - 这样 然后再放下
看我手势
- 我知道了 不用再说了 - 好的
- 我们再来一次 - 好的
来吧 我们可以的 就最后一段
我们倒回去一点 回到C段
开始点火 熄灯
- 熄灯 - 熄灯 点火
好的 休息十分钟
(奥利安斯·帕纳加里斯 吉他手) 我太高兴了
MJ和我们一起彩排 我的梦想终于成真了
他真的来了 太不可思议了 真是太酷了
我非常喜欢他
谢谢
(巴什利·约翰逊 打击乐手) 迈克尔
是我们时代最伟大的艺人
和迈克尔同台表演让我激动不已
(莫·普雷修 键盘/吉他手) 从他8岁时我就一直是MJ的粉丝
和他一起工作是我的一直以来的梦想
我和很多出色的艺术家合作过
但我得说 他的表演让人赏心悦目
(亚历克斯·阿尔 贝斯手)
迈克尔是个完美主义者
这在现在的流行乐坛并不常见
你可骗不了迈克尔
你得真的熟悉他的唱片
幸运的话 你会提高自己
(乔纳森·修格伏特·莫菲特 鼓手)
他是个表演天才
他的很有才能 功底深厚而且富有创造性
能够深入人心 他的才能无人能及
就是这儿
怎么还有一个音节 对不起 打断一下
这儿有个错误 没有第二个音节 大家都停一下
第一音节之后 我们就开始过渡
- 再来一次 - 好的
- 从头开始吗 - 是的
- 这就是彩排的必要性 - 开始 走位
"Black Or White"
I took my baby on a Saturday bang
Boy is that girl with you yes we're one and the same
Now I believe in miracles
And a miracle has happened tonight
Thinking about my baby
It don't matter if you're black or white
然后我们跑到这儿来
I am tired of this devil
I am tired of this stuff
I am tired of this business
Sew when the going gets rough
I aing t scared of your brother
I aing t scared of no sheets
I aing t scared of nobody
Girl when the going gets mean
Protection for gangs, clubs, and nations
Causing grief in human relations it's a turf war
On a global scale
I'd rather hear both sides of the tale
See, it's not about races
Just places faces
Where your blood comes from is where your space is
I've seen the bright get duller
I'm not going to spend my life being a color
Don't tell me you agree with me
When I saw you kicking dirt in my eye
But, if you're thinking about my baby
It don't matter if you're black or white
I said if you're thinking of being my baby
Thinking of being my brother
It don't matter if you're black or white
It's black, it's white
It's tough for them to get by
Sit's black, it's white
It's black, it's white
他们停下来的时候 你就弹到最高音
这个时候轮到你独奏
高音 长高音
要最高的
就看你的了 大家都支持你
(汤米·奥根 吉他手)
让人印象深刻
我们是在见证天才
他就是国王 同时又是个很谦逊的人
他就是音乐的化身 你还要期待什么
我们都只是调味品
快看 真是太美了
给我看看第二个
- 就像是灵魂的爆发 - 是的
- 都是金色的 看这儿 - 我太喜欢这一缕阳光了
这简直太...
我非常尊重大自然的神秘和奇幻
所以看到这个世界发生的这些事之后
我真的很气愤
在亚马逊 据说每一秒
都有相当于一块足球场那么大的绿地被毁坏
这种事一直在困扰我
所以我写了这类的歌曲
来唤起人类的良知
我热爱我们的地球 我热爱森林
我喜欢看树木的颜色 树叶的变化
我热爱并尊重大自然
"Earth Song"
What about sunrise
What about rain
What about all the things
That you said we were to gain...
What about flowering fields
Is there a time
What about all the things
That you said was yours and mine
Did you ever stop to notice
All the blood we've shed before
The crying earth the weeping shores?
What have we done to the world
Look what we've done
What about all the peace
That you pledge your only son
What about flowering fields
Is there a time
What about all the dreams
That you said was yours and mine
Did you ever stop to notice
All the children dead from war
The crying earth the weeping shores
I used to dream
I used to glance beyond the stars
Now I don't know where we are
Although I know
Hey, what about yesterday, what about us
What about the lie, what about us
What about yesterday, what about us
What about my time, what about us
What about everything, what about us
How can I end it, what about us
What about everything
What about the damn
What about everyting, what about us
It's emptying, what about us
What about every man, what about us
What about my dream, what about us
What about everything, what about us
I get it all fine, what about us
What about every being
What about the damn
What about everything
What about the man, what about us
What about every lane, what about us
He get it nasty, what about us
What about all the kids, what about us
What about the dream, what about us
What about everything
What about the damn
如果这样的话效果会更好
让它继续轰鸣
它响一会儿之后 慢慢的安静
那个门开了之后 钢琴响起
上帝保佑你
让人感觉到大自然在
为人类的种种罪行而煎熬
因为地球已经生病了 就像发烧了
如果现在不及时补救 就来不及了
这是我们补救的唯一机会
就像是行驶的火车
是时候了 就是现在了
我爱你们
当我说出这些之后 我们就结束
人们总是说"会有人去管的"
政府或者别的人会去管的 谁会管呢
就该从我做起 不要指望别人
灯光效果组注意
首先 迈克尔会先上台来
手提箱动作
在这儿 迈克尔会停在这儿
然后走到这儿 灯光会跟着他动
- 好的 - 好的 然后你向前走
他完全进入了灯光
- 我想这样进入光圈 - 可以 他走到这里之后
为什么不做一些迈克尔标志性动作
做个手势之后 光效持续到这里
不管灯光当时是怎样
光效继续 你走到舞台中央的灯光中
开始表演
"Billie Jean"
She was more like a beauty queen from a movie scene
I said don't mind, but what do you mean I am the one
Who will dance on the floor in the round
She said I am the one
She told me her name was Billie Jean, as she caused a scene
Then every head turned with eyes that dreamed of being the one
Who will dance on the floor in the round
People always told me be careful of what you do
And don't go around breaking young girls' hearts
And mother always told me be careful of who you love
And be careful of what you do ['cause the lie becomes the truth]
Billie Jean is not my lover
She's just a girl who claims that I am the one
But the kid is not my son
She says I am the one, but the kid is not my son
She knew what we knew on that time
'Cause we danced on the floor in the round
So take my strong advice, just remember to always think twice
Do think twice
She told my baby we'd danced till three, then she looked at me
Then showed a photo my baby cried his eyes were like mine
'Cause we danced on the floor in the round
People always told me be careful of what you do
And don't go around breaking young girls' hearts
She came and stood right by me
Then the smell of sweet perfume
This happened much too soon
She called me [to her room]
Billie Jean is not my lover
She's just a girl who claims that I am the one
But the kid is not my son
Billie Jean is not my lover
She's just a girl who claims that I am the one
But the kid is not my son
She says I am the one, but the kid is not my son
She says I am the one
But the kid is not my son
Billie Jean is not my lover
She's just a girl who claims that I am the one
But the kid is not my son
She says I am the one, but the kid is not my son
She says I am the one
She say he is my son
Billie Jean is not my lover
至少完整地来了一遍
上帝保佑你们
像身在教堂一样
摇滚乐的教堂
- 我是你的超级粉丝 - 上帝保佑你们
- 喝点水吧 - 喝点水 去喝点水吧
我只想说作为迈克尔的搭档
这是我创作生涯最不同寻常的经历
我倍感自豪 激动和兴奋
感谢所有人作出的巨大努力
迈克尔来说点什么吧
每个人都很棒
继续坚持 保持信念
我能看到你们的坚忍 耐心 和体谅
这是一次历险 一次不同寻常的历险
不过没有什么好担心的
只是一次美妙的经历
把观众带入从未有过的境界
向他们展示前所未有的才能
尽情释放自已 我爱你们
我们是一家 我们就是一个大家庭
- 就是这样 - 对 阿门
让爱回归到这个世界
提醒这个世界爱的重要
爱不可或缺 互相关爱 我们是个整体
珍惜这个星球 我们还有4年时间来弥补
等到破坏不可逆转 我们就完了
我们要传递一个重要的信息 知道吗
非常感谢你们所有人的合作 谢谢
上帝保佑大家
过个愉快的周日 保重身体
让我们齐喊 1 2 3 迈克尔
接下来我们要做"镜中人"的彩排
然后再来讨论结尾 手语部分
- 他的最爱 - 没错
- 他很喜欢 - 你们得跟着迈克尔做的一样
- 不 不 不 - 你知道自己很喜欢的
这个动作最棒 我的最爱
我三年级的时候 最爱的歌就是
"镜中人"
能够在舞台上和迈克尔和声 真的很酷
能够和他同台表演真的很不可思议
他是个非同寻常的艺人
And no message could have been any clearer
If you wanna make the world a better place
Take a look at yourself and then make a change
I'm starting with the man in the mirror
I'm asking him to change his ways
And no message could have been any clearer
If you wanna make the world a better place
Take a look at yourself and then make that change
I'm starting with the man in the mirror
I'm asking him to change his ways
No message could have been any clearer
If you wanna make the world a better place
Take a look at yourself and then make the change
You gotta get it right, while you got the time
'Cause when you close your heart
Then you close your mind
If you wanna make the world a better place
Take a look at yourself then make that change
I'm gonna make a change
It's gonna feel real good
Sure mon (Change)
Just lift yourself
You know, you got to stop it yourself
Make that change
Yeah, make my change today
You got, you got to move
You'll love it, you'll love it
You got to stand up, stand up, stand up
Stand up and lift yourself, now
You know it, you know it, you know it, you know
Michael Jackson
永远的流行天王
爱将永存
Make that change...
"This is it"
This is it, here I stand
I'm the light of the world, I feel grand
Got this love I can feel
And I know yes for sure it is real
And it feels as though I've seen your face a thousand times
And you said you really know me to yourself
And I know that you have got addicted with your eyes
But you say you gonna live it for yourself.
I never heard a single word about you
Falling in love wasn't my plan
I never thought that I would be your lover
C'mon baby, just understand
This is it, I can say,
I'm the light of the world, run away
We can feel, this is real
Every time I'm in love that I feel
And I feel as though I've known you since a thousand years
And you tell me that you've seen my face before.
And you said to me you don't want me hanging round
Many times, wanna do it here before, oh, yeah
I never heard a single word about you
Falling in love wasn't my plan
I never thought that I would be your lover
C'mon baby, just understand
This is it, I can feel
I'm the light of the world, this is real
Feel my song, we can say
And I tell you I feel that way
And I feel as though I've known you for a thousand years
And you said you want some of this yourself
And you said won't you go with me, on a while
And I know that it's really cool myself
I never heard a single word about you
Falling in love wasn't my plan
I never thought that I would be your lover
C'mon baby, just understand, oh, yeah
I never heard a single word about you
Falling in love wasn't my plan
I never thought that I would be your lover
C'mon baby, just understand, oh, yeah
I never heard a single word about you
Falling in love wasn't my plan
I never thought that I would be your lover
C'mon baby...
"Heal the World"
There's a place in your heart
And I know that it is love
And this place could be much brighter than tomorrow
And if you really try
You'll find there's no need to cry
In this place you'll feel there's no hurt or sorrow
There are ways to get there
If you care enough for the living
Make a little space
Make a better place
Heal the world
Make it a better place
For you and for me
And the entire human race
There are people dying
If you care enough for the living
Make it a better place
For you and for me
Heal the world,heal the world
Make it a better place
For you and for me
And the entire human race
There are people dying
If you care enough for the living
Make it a better place
For you and for me, you and for me
Heal the world we are living
Saving for our children
"Human Nature"
If this town
Is just an apple
Then let me take a bite
If they say
Why, why, tell 'em that it's Human Nature
Why, why, does he do me that way
If they say
Why, why, tell 'em that it's Human Nature
Why, why does he do me that way
Why, why, why
Why, why, does he do me that way
If they say
Why, why, why, why
Tell 'em...why, why
I like loving this way
Reaching out
先不要动 好吗
我深呼吸 然后走进来
先把纽扣解开
环顾一下四周
打几个响指
拯救世界
我爱你们 迈克尔
仅以此片献给迈克尔·杰克逊的孩子